[
	{
		"question": "Who created Flutter?",
		"options": [ "Facebook", "Adobe", "Google", "Microsoft" ],
		"answer": "Google"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is Flutter?",
		"options": [
			"Android Development Kit",
			"IOS Development Kit",
			"Web Development Kit",
			"SDK to build beautiful IOS, Android, Web & Desktop Native Apps"
		],
		"answer": "SDK to build beautiful IOS, Android, Web & Desktop Native Apps"
	},
	{
		"question": "Which programing language is used by Flutter",
		"options": [ "Ruby", "Dart", "C++", "Kotlin" ],
		"answer": "Dart"
	},
	{
		"question": "How many programming languages are in use?",
		"options": [ "20", "50", "2000", "5000" ],
		"answer": "2000"
	},
	{
		"question": "Who founded Apple Computer?",
		"options": [ "Steve Jobs", "Sheryl Sandberg", "Bill Gates", "Sundar Pichai" ],
		"answer": "Steve Jobs"
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of these is not a peripheral, in computer terms?",
		"options": [ "Keyboard", "Mouse", "Motherboard", "Monitor" ],
		"answer": "Motherboard"
	},
	{
		"question": "When was the first alpha version of Flutter released?",
		"options": [ "2016", "2017", "2018", "2019" ],
		"answer": "2017"
	},
	{
		"question": "A network designed to allow communication within an organization is called:",
		"options": [ "the Internet", "the Intranet", "a browser", "the World Wide Web" ],
		"answer": "the Intranet"
	},
	{
		"question": "Who created Dart programing language?",
		"options": [ "Lars Bak and Kasper Lund", "Brendan Eich", "Bjarne Stroustrup", "Jeremy Ashkenas" ],
		"answer": "Lars Bak and Kasper Lund"
	},
	{
		"question": "Is Flutter for Desktop stable?",
		"options": [ "Yes", "No" ],
		"answer": "No"
	},
	{
		"question": "Is Flutter for Web stable?",
		"options": [ "Yes", "No" ],
		"answer": "Yes"
	}
]
